[
  {
    "questionText": "Catch the even number",
    "questionFields": [
      "2",
      "4",
      "6",
      "_"
    ],
    "options": [
      "8",
      "2",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "Catch the even number",
    "questionFields": [
      "14",
      "16",
      "18",
      "_"
    ],
    "options": [
      "14",
      "20",
      "22"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "20"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "Catch the odd number",
    "questionFields": [
      "_",
      "5",
      "7",
      "9"
    ],
    "options": [
      "-1",
      "3",
      "1"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "Catch the odd number",
    "questionFields": [
      "11",
      "13",
      "15",
      "_"
    ],
    "options": [
      "15",
      "13",
      "17"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "17"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "Catch the even number",
    "questionFields": [
      "10",
      "12",
      "_",
      "16"
    ],
    "options": [
      "14",
      "18",
      "12"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "14"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "Catch the even number",
    "questionFields": [
      "_",
      "8",
      "10",
      "12"
    ],
    "options": [
      "10",
      "6",
      "0"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "Catch the even number",
    "questionFields": [
      "_",
      "18",
      "20",
      "22"
    ],
    "options": [
      "16",
      "22",
      "10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "16"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "Catch the even number",
    "questionFields": [
      "_",
      "2",
      "4",
      "6"
    ],
    "options": [
      "2",
      "-2",
      "0"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "0"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "Catch the even number",
    "questionFields": [
      "18",
      "_",
      "22",
      "24"
    ],
    "options": [
      "24",
      "20",
      "22"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "20"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "Catch the odd number",
    "questionFields": [
      "13",
      "15",
      "_",
      "19"
    ],
    "options": [
      "17",
      "19",
      "11"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "17"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "Catch the odd number",
    "questionFields": [
      "23",
      "_",
      "27",
      "29"
    ],
    "options": [
      "25",
      "23",
      "29"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "25"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "Catch the odd number",
    "questionFields": [
      "_",
      "27",
      "29",
      "31"
    ],
    "options": [
      "25",
      "27",
      "19"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "25"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "Catch the odd number",
    "questionFields": [
      "9",
      "_",
      "13",
      "15"
    ],
    "options": [
      "13",
      "15",
      "11"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "11"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "Catch the odd number",
    "questionFields": [
      "5",
      "_",
      "9",
      "11"
    ],
    "options": [
      "5",
      "3",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "Catch the even number",
    "questionFields": [
      "4",
      "6",
      "_",
      "10"
    ],
    "options": [
      "14",
      "8",
      "10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "Catch the odd number",
    "questionFields": [
      "19",
      "21",
      "23",
      "_"
    ],
    "options": [
      "25",
      "21",
      "19"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "25"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "Catch the odd number",
    "questionFields": [
      "1",
      "3",
      "_",
      "7"
    ],
    "options": [
      "11",
      "5",
      "-1"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "Catch the odd number",
    "questionFields": [
      "21",
      "_",
      "25",
      "27"
    ],
    "options": [
      "23",
      "19",
      "21"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "23"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "Catch the even number",
    "questionFields": [
      "_",
      "28",
      "30",
      "32"
    ],
    "options": [
      "32",
      "26",
      "20"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "26"
  },
  {
    "questionText": "Catch the odd number",
    "questionFields": [
      "17",
      "_",
      "21",
      "23"
    ],
    "options": [
      "21",
      "13",
      "19"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "19"
  }
]